(Sanada) I want to be an idol with everyone.
(sob)
“I want to be an idol with everyone.”
Thank you for your hard work
Were you watching it again?
After all, it would be a waste to quit like this.
Look for an office where you can take on the challenge even now.
Why don't you just continue being an idol, Sanada-kun?
There are so many people supporting me...
I don't like it, then.
I…
It's no good unless you're an eternal boy.
I see...
I guess as you get older you get used to giving up.
Isn't life a series of things that can't be helped?
That's why I gradually become addicted to it.
(Yamanaka) Even you said, "It can't be helped."
yes
but…
Eternal Boy taught me this, right?
♬～
(2 people) I…
Say it first
Mr. Yamanaka, please say it first.
still…
I don't want to give up
♬～
I was thinking the same thing too
Hehehehe
(Imagawa) It's late. We're both tired of waiting. (Asai)
Didn't everyone leave?
(Ishida) It can't be helped that we break up. We're not young enough to complain.
But it's okay to have a little struggle at the end.
Me too...
But the venue... (Kakizaki) I've already figured it out.
I said I could pay later because it would be offset against sales.
Let's do it live
I want everyone to sing "Again" at the end.
Yes ah
♬Uuuuuuuuuuuuuu
♬～
♬The words “See you” make me feel lonely.
♬(Asai) For some reason, I feel so loved by ordinary moments.
♬Me in the middle of a long road
♬(Kakizaki) It was you who found me
♬(Imagawa) Stop and listen to this voice
♬(Ishida) Thank you for giving it to me.
♬(All) Again (Hey) Again (Hey) Again (Hey)
♬What I want to tell you
♬Again (Yeah) Again (Yeah) Again (Yeah)
♬Today is forever
♬Again (Hey) Again (Hey) Again (Hey)
♬We'll meet again someday
♬Again (Yeah) Again (Yeah) Again (Yeah)
♬ Repeat this voice
♬It's not like you're only worrying about the future you can't see.
♬No matter what happens, for some reason I think it's okay
♬I can hear your voice no matter where I am
♬No matter how far away the place is
♬ Being able to be by my side like this now
♬I think it's a miracle
♬(Everyone) Again (Hey) Again (Hey) Again (Hey)
♬The days I spent with you
♬Again (Yeah) Again (Yeah) Again (Yeah)
♬It shines more than anything
♬Again (Hey) Again (Hey) Again (Hey)
♬Your existence
♬Again (Yeah) Again (Yeah) Again (Yeah)
♬Keep supporting me
♬(Kakizaki/Ishida) The time I thought “someday” has come
♬I don't need tears
♬(Yamanaka/Imagawa) Show me your smile
♬(Everyone) Again (Hey) Again (Hey) Again (Hey)
♬What I want to tell you
♬Again (Yeah) Again (Yeah) Again (Yeah)
♬Today is forever
♬Again (Hey) Again (Hey) Again (Hey)
♬We'll meet again someday
♬Again (Yeah) Again (Yeah) Again (Yeah)
♬ Repeat this voice
♬～
(cheers)
Eternal Boy will forever be in everyone's heart.
Thank you everyone
(Audience) Thank you!
♬～
≪For 35 years, I have lived a dull and normal life≫
≪That's fine≫
≪That's good≫
≪While saying that≫
≪But...≫
everyone key
Disbanding...
I don't think they'll break up
Eternal Shonen will not disband and will be on hiatus.
that's why…
Don't lose your key
I'll be using it again soon
Hehehe
Let's go
yes
♬～
“Eikyu Shonen”?
Nikolai Asakura: Besides cooking, he also takes care of us.
I want to see more scenery with this member.
(Fukuko) Eternal boy, start!
But you can't do it, right? I hope you get better from now on.
(Imagawa) Sanayan...
(Ren) Let's have a comedy competition, shall we? Comedy competition?
yes cheese
Did you see it?
(Together) Eternal youth!
(Manda) It leads to a come-from-behind home run.
｟Hahahaha｠
(cheers)
Was Eternal Boy really that easy?
I want to be an idol with everyone
♬～